

# PETER LUK

user experience designer digital marketer

I practice user centered design principles based on the need of the business and their audiences to help achieve harmony between the user and the business. I believe that marketing and user exerpiece should go hand in hand because ultimately, it's the audience that we market to who will use and experience the products.

### Selected Experience

### Blocklub Studio

Founder

Jan 2014 - Present

Organize information to create visualizations of content to achieve brands objective by sequencing and relating elements; preparing storyboards; applying principles of HCI, comprehension, learning, and aesthetics

Create and present UX deliverables such as wireframes, prototypes and final mockups to effectively communicate interaction and design ideas.

Research potential market segmentations, identify the current market trend and adapt relative design to the potential market. Collaboration with comic artists to enhance on the user's needs.

Work with product & research team to define research methodologies and participate in user testing or fieldwork and the presentation of findings as required

Design web, mobile and social experiences

### Evilnut Technology

Digital Marketing Coordinator & UI Designer

November 2014 - May 2015

Develop and execute digital marketing campaigns for Evilnut's programs, services, and events

Design and implementation of wireframe sketches and high fidelity prototypes through frequent collaboration with developers. I went through the design process of this project with a team of designers and developers. At the end of the project, we were to create a interactive prototype and do field testing with it.

Manage the planning, communications, logistics and execution of Evilnut's Government funding announcements and other events

Create and execute Google Adwords PPC campaigns as well as analyze web traffic and data, using Hubspot, Marketo and Google Analytics

Work with product & development team to create the launch event of 2015, which in returned helped the company increased exposure rate by 25% and drove traffic up by 5%.

### Cymax

Marketing Coordinator

December 2013 - September 2014

Built, identified and maintained online strategy for clients via Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, LinkedIn, Tumblr.

Monitored benchmarks and measured impact of social media initiatives as well as setting up email templates and webforms design & write copy for emails

Worked jointly with IT and Merchandising to constantly improve the quality and performance of the landing pages, and to increase conversion rates. Managed and optimized the company's dynamic display remarketing campaigns, and created AdWords script to facilitate keyword expansion.

Coordinated the implementation of Universal Analytics and Enhanced Ecommerce through Google Tag Manager, by thoroughly planning out necessary data layer structure across all page types.

Daily use of: DoubleClick Search, Google AdWords, Bing Ads, Microsoft Excel, IBM Cognos, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager, Facebook Ads.



# PETER LUK

user experience designer digital marketer

#### Selected Achievements

### Head Coach for Pinetree Secondary-First place in Province

Coached and lead pinetree secondary senior badminton team and won the provinical champion-ship in 2010, runner up in 2011, and lastly third in 2012. Guided many students to better value their time and education while focusing on what matters to them most.

### Nominated to Present at the Cityhall Open House of Vancouver

For my second year university course: IAT 235 information design, My team and I were tasked to design and develop a responsive website that is user friendly and easy for those who wishes to learn a bit more on retrofitting and how it may benefit them. Through researching on data provided by City hall of Vancouver, we were able to generate multiple personas which our design is based upon. The design process consists of up to 50 detailed low fidelity wireframes and sketches, then after we chosen a selective few that we believe may benefit the user most, our professor and teaching staff will critique on our choices. Afterwards, we began implementing high fidelity mockups and after more revisions, we implement actual programming process.

## Performance Evaluation Design Selected by City of Coquitlam

Recently, I had the opportunity to redesign the performance evaluation sheets for the recreation department at the City of Coquitlam. I started out as a program coordinator that teaches youth badminton during saturday mornings but upon viewing their evaluation sheets, I found that it was extremely convoluted. I took the initiative of re-designing the form for the city. They saw the final high fidelity mockups and approved my design.

### Skills Marketing Applications

market research and analysis, Branding and segmentation, Google analytics, Social Media communications, email campaign

### Software

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, Hootsuite, MailChimp, Twitter, Facebook

### Product Design

Interactive Design, Rapid Prototyping, User Research, Information Architect, Usability testing

### Languages

HTML5/CSS3, Java, JQuery, JavaScript

English, Cantonese, Mandarin

### Technical Skills

html, css, jquery, google analytics, mailchimp, photoshop, illustrator, marketo, financial analysis and forecasting

### Education

### Simon Fraser University

Beedie School of Business

2008 - 2013

Enrolled as a science student, I transferred into business originally under the pressure of my family. Intitally I couldn't see the value of the courses, however during an internship, I was able to apply what I've learnt, allowing me to see the bigger picture and fall in love with marketing

### British Columbia Institute of Technology

Applied Web Development

2016 - 2018

I firmly believe that in order to better understand our world and how things operate in the future, web development is one of the most important things to learn. Having the skills to code allows us many possibilities, you can be a developer, create softwares, web development or start something of your own.